<?xml version='1.0'?>
<song>[{"lyrics":"(I've been mad for fucking years\nAbsolutely years\nBeen over the edge for yonks\nBeen working me buns off for bands\n\nI've always been mad, I know I've been mad\nLike the most of us\nIt's very hard to explain why you're mad\nEven if you're not mad)","filePath":"Speak-To-Me.txt","songName":"Speak To Me","writerName":"WATERS MASON","source":"web","albumName":"The Dark Side of the Moon","artistName":"Pink-Floyd","youtubePath":"N/A","releaseDate":"1973-03-01"},{"lyrics":"Breathe, breathe in the air\nDon't be afraid to care\nLeave but don't leave me\nLook around and choose your own ground\n\nLong you live and high you fly\nAnd smiles you'll give and tears you'll cry\nAnd all you touch and all you see\nIs all your life will ever be\n\nRun, rabbit run\nDig that hole, forget the sun\nAnd when at last the work is done\nDon't sit down it's time to dig another one\n\nFor long you live and high you fly\nBut only if you ride the tide\nAnd balanced on the biggest wave\nYou race towards an early grave","filePath":"Breathe.txt","songName":"Breathe","writerName":"ROGER WATERS","source":"web","albumName":"The Dark Side of the Moon","artistName":"Pink-Floyd","youtubePath":"N/A","releaseDate":"1973-03-01"},{"lyrics":"[female announcer, announcing flights at airport, including 'Rome']\n\"Live for today, gone tomorrow, that's me, HaHaHaaaaaa!\"\n\n(Instrumental)","filePath":"On-The-Run.txt","songName":"On The Run","writerName":"Waters, Gilmour, Wright","source":"web","albumName":"The Dark Side of the Moon","artistName":"Pink-Floyd","youtubePath":"N/A","releaseDate":"1973-03-01"},{"lyrics":"Ticking away the moments that make up a dull day\nYou fritter and waste the hours in an offhand way\nKicking around on a piece of ground in your home town\nWaiting for someone or something to show you the way\n\nTired of lying in the sunshine staying home to watch the rain\nYou are young and life is long and there is time to kill today\nAnd then one day you find ten years have got behind you\nNo one told you when to run, you missed the starting gun\n\nAnd you run and you run to catch up with the sun, but its sinking\nAnd racing around to come up behind you again\nThe sun is the same in a relative way, but you're older\nShorter of breath and one day closer to death\n\nEvery year is getting shorter, never seem to find the time\nPlans that either come to naught or half a page of scribbled lines\nHanging on in quiet desperation is the English way\nThe time has gone, the song is over, thought I'd something more to say\n\nHome, home again\nI like to be here when I can\nAnd when I come home cold and tired\nIt's good to warm my bones beside the fire\nFar away across the field\nThe tolling of the iron bell\nCalls the faithful to their knees\nTo hear the softly spoken magic spells","filePath":"Time.txt","songName":"Time","writerName":"David Jon Gilmour, Nicholas Berkeley Mason, George Roger Waters, Richard William Wright","source":"web","albumName":"The Dark Side of the Moon","artistName":"Pink-Floyd","youtubePath":"N/A","releaseDate":"1973-03-01"},{"lyrics":"\"And I am not frightened of dying, any time will do, I\ndon't mind. Why should I be frightened of dying?\nThere's no reason for it, you've gotta go sometime.\"\n\n\"If you can hear this whispering you are dying.\"\n\n\"I never said I was frightened of dying.\"","filePath":"The-Great-Gig-In-The-Sky.txt","songName":"The Great Gig In The Sky","writerName":"Rick Wright","source":"web","albumName":"The Dark Side of the Moon","artistName":"Pink-Floyd","youtubePath":"N/A","releaseDate":"1973-03-01"},{"lyrics":"Money, get away\nGet a good job with more pay and you're ok\n\nMoney, it's a gas\nGrab that cash with both hands and make a stash\n\nA new car, caviar, four star daydream\nThink I'll buy me a football team\n\nMoney, get back\nI'm all right Jack, keep your hands off of my stack\n\nMoney, it's a hit\nDon't give me that do-goody-good bullshit\n\nI'm in the hi-fidelity first class traveling section\nAnd I think I need a Lear Jet\n\nMoney, it's a crime\nShare it fairly but don't take a slice of my pie\n\nMoney, so they say\nIs the root of all evil today\n\nBut if you ask for a rise it's no surprise\nThat they're giving none away\n\nAway\nAway","filePath":"Money.txt","songName":"Money","writerName":"George Roger Waters","source":"web","albumName":"The Dark Side of the Moon","artistName":"Pink-Floyd","youtubePath":"N/A","releaseDate":"1973-03-01"},{"lyrics":"Us and them\nAnd after all we're only ordinary men\n\nMe and you\nGod only knows it's not what we would choose to do\n\nForward he cried from the rear\nAnd the front rank died\nThe General sat, and the lines on the map\nMoved from side to side\n\nBlack and blue\nAnd who knows which is which and who is who\n\nUp and down\nAnd in the end it's only round and round, and round\n\nHaven't you heard it's a battle of words\nThe poster bearer cried\nListen son, said the man with the gun\nThere's room for you inside\n\nDown and out\nIt can't be helped but there's a lot of it about\n\nWith, without\nAnd who'll deny it's what the fighting's all about\n\nOut of the way, it's a busy day\nI've got things on my mind\nFor want of the price of tea and a slice\nThe old man died","filePath":"Us-And-Them.txt","songName":"Us And Them","writerName":"Richard William Wright, George Roger Waters","source":"web","albumName":"The Dark Side of the Moon","artistName":"Pink-Floyd","youtubePath":"N/A","releaseDate":"1973-03-01"},{"lyrics":"The lunatic is on the grass\nThe lunatic is on the grass\nRemembering games and daisy chains and laughs\nGot to keep the loonies on the path\n\nThe lunatic is in the hall\nThe lunatics are in my hall\nThe paper holds their folded faces to the floor\nAnd everyday the paper boy brings more\n\nAnd if the dam breaks open many years too soon\nAnd if there is no room upon the hill\nAnd if your head explodes with dark forebodings too\nI'll see you on the dark side of the moon\n\nThe lunatic is in my head\nThe lunatic is in my head\nYou raise the blade, you make the change\nYou re-arrange me 'til I'm sane\n\nYou lock the door\nAnd throw away the key\nThere's someone in my head, but it's not me\n\nAnd if the cloud bursts, thunder in your ear\nYou shout and no one seems to hear\nAnd if the band you're in starts playing different tunes\nI'll see you on the dark side of the moon\n\nI can't think of anything to say except\nI think it's marvelous! Hahaha!","filePath":"Brain-Damage.txt","songName":"Brain Damage","writerName":"George Roger Waters","source":"web","albumName":"The Dark Side of the Moon","artistName":"Pink-Floyd","youtubePath":"https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DVQ3-Xe_suY","releaseDate":"1973-03-01"},{"lyrics":"All that you touch, and\nAll that you see, and\nAll that you taste, and\nAll you feel, and\nAll that you love, and\nAll that you hate, and\nAll you mistrust, and\nAll you save, and\nAll that you give, and\nAll that you deal, and\nAll that you buy,\nBeg, borrow, or steal, and\nAll you create, and\nAll you destroy, and\nAll that you do, and\nAll that you say, and\nAll that you eat, and\nEveryone you meet, and\nAll that you slight, and\nEveryone you fight, and\nAll that is now, and\nAll that is gone, and\nAll that's to come, and\nEverything under the sun is in tune\nBut the sun is eclipsed by the moon\n\nThere is no dark side of the moon, really\nMatter of fact it's all dark","filePath":"Eclipse.txt","songName":"Eclipse","writerName":"George Roger Waters","source":"web","albumName":"The Dark Side of the Moon","artistName":"Pink-Floyd","youtubePath":"N/A","releaseDate":"1973-03-01"}]</song>